{
    "subject": "resource/Philippines",
    "predicate": "ontology/capital",
    "object": "resource/Manila",
    "human_readable": "The capital of Philippines is Manila.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9509966969490051,
            "question": "What is the capital of the Philippines?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8009032011032104,
            "question": "Is Manila a city or a country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7227176427841187,
            "question": "Where is Manila located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.631782591342926,
            "question": "What is the history of Manila?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5848219990730286,
            "question": "When was Manila founded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5407175421714783,
            "question": "What are some notable landmarks in Manila?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48125866055488586,
            "question": "What is the population of Manila?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3218735158443451,
            "question": "Name a famous person from Manila."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1811906397342682,
            "question": "What are some popular Filipino dishes enjoyed in Manila?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1584787219762802,
            "question": "What is the official language spoken in Manila?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The capital of Philippines is Manila.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9081_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular Filipino dishes enjoyed in Manila?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9081_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a famous person from Manila.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9081_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the population of Manila?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9081_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9081_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9081_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9081_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9081_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9081_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9081_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9081_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9081_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9081_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9081_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format for the query \"The capital of Philippines is Manila\":\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\n* All documents contain information that confirms Manila as the capital of the Philippines. \n\nDocument 1 states: \"Manila is the capital of the Philippines.\"\n\nDocument 2 states: \"The City of Manila is the capital of the Philippines.\"\n\nDocument 3 states: \"Manila is the capital of the Philippines.\"\n\nDocument 4 states: \"The capital of Philippines is Manila , which was founded 1571 .\"\n\nDocument 5 states: \"Manila (i/m\u0259\u02c8n\u026al.\u0259/) is the capital city of the Philippines.\"\n\nDocument 6 states: \"Manila (Wikipedia), one of sixteen cities that compose Metro Manila, is the capital of the Philippines.\"\n\nTherefore, based on the information provided in all documents, it can be concluded that the triple \"The capital of Philippines is Manila\" is correct."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents collectively confirm that the capital of the Philippines is indeed Manila, which supports the given statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}